Edward Livingston Papers, 1683-1877 (bulk 1764-1836 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 17: Papers Related to Landholdings, 1683-1887; 11 boxes
  - Subseries 17H: Miscellaneous Landholding Papers, 1706-1887; 3 boxes
    - Miscellaneous Surveys and Survey Maps, 1740-1887; 4 folders (Box B-000061, Folder 6-9)
    - Miscellaneous Survey Map, undated; 1 item (Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- 32101037100011 (Box 1)
- 32101037100029 (Box 2)
- 32101037100037 (Box 3)
- 32101037100045 (Box 4)
- 32101037100052 (Box 5)
- 32101037100060 (Box 6)
- 32101037100078 (Box 7)
- 32101037100086 (Box 8)
- 32101037100094 (Box 9)
- 32101037100102 (Box 10)
- 32101037100110 (Box 11)
- 32101037100128 (Box 12)
- 32101037100136 (Box 13)
- 32101037100144 (Box 14)
- 32101037100151 (Box 15)
- 32101037100169 (Box 16)
- 32101037100177 (Box 17)
- 32101037100185 (Box 18)
- 32101037100193 (Box 19)
- 32101037100201 (Box 20)
- 32101037100219 (Box 21)
- 32101037100227 (Box 22)
- 32101037100235 (Box 23)
- 32101037100243 (Box 24)
- 32101037100250 (Box 25)
- 32101037100268 (Box 26)
- 32101037100276 (Box 27)
- 32101037100284 (Box 28)
- 32101037100292 (Box 29)
- 32101037100300 (Box 30)
- 32101037100318 (Box 31)
- 32101037100326 (Box 32)
- 32101037100334 (Box 33)
- 32101037100342 (Box 34)
- 32101037100359 (Box 35)
- 32101037100367 (Box 36)
- 32101037100375 (Box 37)
- 32101037100383 (Box 38)
- 32101037100391 (Box 39)
- 32101037100409 (Box 40)
- 32101037100417 (Box 41)
- 32101037100425 (Box 42)
- 32101037100433 (Box 43)
- 32101037100441 (Box 44)
- 32101037100458 (Box 45)
- 32101037100466 (Box 46)
- 32101037100474 (Box 47)
- 32101037100482 (Box 48)
- 32101037100490 (Box 49)
- 32101037100508 (Box 50)
- 32101037100516 (Box 51)
- 32101037100524 (Box 52)
- 32101037100532 (Box 53)
- 32101037100540 (Box 54)
- 32101037100557 (Box 55)
- 32101037100565 (Box 56)
- 32101037100573 (Box 57)
- 32101037100581 (Box 58)
- 32101037100599 (Box 59)
- 32101037100607 (Box 60)
- 32101037100615 (Box 61)
- 32101037100623 (Box 62)
- 32101037100631 (Box 63)
- 32101037100649 (Box 64)
- 32101037100656 (Box 65)
- 32101037100664 (Box 66)
- 32101037100672 (Box 67)
- 32101037100680 (Box 68)
- 32101080848078 (Box P-000007)
- 32101037100698 (Box 69)
- 32101037100706 (Box 70)
- 32101037100714 (Box 71)
- 32101037100722 (Box 72)
- 32101037100730 (Box 73)
- 32101037100748 (Box 74)
- 32101037100755 (Box 75)
- 32101037100763 (Box 76)
- 32101037100771 (Box 77)
- 32101037100789 (Box 78)
- 32101037100797 (Box 79)
- 32101037088000 (Box 80)
- 32101037088018 (Box 81)
- 32101037088026 (Box 82)
- 32101037088034 (Box 83)
- 32101037088042 (Box 84)
- 32101037088059 (Box 85)
- 32101037088067 (Box 86)
- 32101037088075 (Box 87)
- 32101037088083 (Box 88)
- 32101037088091 (Box 89)
- 32101080848086 (Box P-000008)
- 32101037088109 (Box 90)
- 32101037088117 (Box 91)
- 32101080598988 (Box 92)
- 32101080598970 (Box 93)
- 32101037088141 (Box 94)
- 32101080599010 (Box P-000004)
- 32101080848060 (Box P-000006)
- 32101037555479 (Box 163)
- 32101037088158 (Box 95)
- 32101037088166 (Box 96)
- 32101037088174 (Box 97)
- 32101037088182 (Box 98)
- 32101080848094 (Box P-000009)
- 32101037088190 (Box 99)
- 32101037088323 (Box 100)
- 32101037088331 (Box 101)
- 32101037088216 (Box 102)
- 32101080598889 (Box 103)
- 32101037088232 (Box 104)
- 32101037088240 (Box 105)
- 32101037088257 (Box 106)
- 32101037088265 (Box 107)
- 32101037088273 (Box 108)
- 32101037088281 (Box 109)
- 32101037088299 (Box 110)
- 32101037088307 (Box 111)
- 32101080598871 (Box 112)
- 32101037088224 (Box 113)
- 32101037088349 (Box 114)
- 32101037088356 (Box 115)
- 32101037088364 (Box 116)
- 32101037088372 (Box 117)
- 32101037088380 (Box 118)
- 32101037088398 (Box 119)
- 32101080848102 (Box P-000010)
- 32101037088406 (Box 120)
- 32101037088414 (Box 121)
- 32101037088422 (Box 122)
- 32101037088430 (Box 123)
- 32101080598962 (Box 124)
- 32101080598897 (Box 125)
- 32101080598913 (Box 126)
- 32101080598954 (Box 127)
- 32101080848136 (Box P-000013)
- 32101037088489 (Box 128)
- 32101080598905 (Box 129)
- 32101080848110 (Box P-000011)
- 32101037088505 (Box 130)
- 32101080598947 (Box 131)
- 32101037088521 (Box 132)
- 32101037088539 (Box 133)
- 32101037088547 (Box 134)
- 32101037088554 (Box 135)
- 32101037088562 (Box 136)
- 32101037088570 (Box 137)
- 32101037088588 (Box 138)
- 32101037088596 (Box 139)
- 32101080523093 (Box 170)
- 32101037088604 (Box 140)
- 32101037088612 (Box 141)
- 32101037088620 (Box 142)
- 32101037088638 (Box 143)
- 32101037088646 (Box 144)
- 32101037088653 (Box 145)
- 32101037088661 (Box 146)
- 32101080598939 (Box 147)
- 32101037088687 (Box 148)
- 32101080848128 (Box P-000012)
- 32101037088711 (Box 149)
- 32101080598921 (Box 150)
- 32101080516295 (Box 164)
- 32101080599218 (Box 151)
- 32101080599200 (Box 152)
- 32101080599192 (Box 153)
- 32101080599184 (Box 154)
- 32101080599176 (Box 155)
- 32101080599168 (Box 156)
- 32101080599150 (Box 157)
- 32101080599143 (Box 158)
- 32101080848052 (Box P-000005)
- 32101080599135 (Box 159)
- 32101080599077 (Box 177)